# JHONATAN SILVÉRIO DE OLIVEIRA

#### **Contato:**

Portifolio: https://portifolio-jhojso.vercel.app/ GitHub: https://github.com/Jh0wjso Telefone: +55 14 9 99798 - 1721

Email: jhonatansilverio1258@gmail.com

## **SUMMARY**

I have been studying software development since 2019 working as a freelancer for over a year, with web applications I have already developed some applications for physical stores did not have **WEB** that applications, and Landing Pages for other businesses and always concerned about the experience and using data metrics to achieve high retention rates I have already created four mobile applications, my specialties are React, React Native, JavaScript, TailwindCSS, NextJs, NestJS. PHP, Elixir.

## **TECNOLOGIES**

- ReactJS
- NextJs
- React Native
- JavaScipt
- NodeJs
- NestJs
- Prisma ORM
- SQL
- Elixir
- Git / GitHub

- PHP
- C#
- .NET
- TypeScript
- Python
- Java
- SpringBoot
- MySQL
- Postgresql

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Software Engenieer - Operately**

Software Engenieer *05/2023 - 06/2024* 

I was a software engineer at Operately, an innovative startup based in Serbia. I recently participated in a two-month open source project, where I demonstrated my versatility as a full stack developer. During this period, I worked with several modern technologies, including Elixir, React, TypeScript and GraphQL. In addition to programming, he also contributes to interface design and backend systems architecture, ensuring that Operately projects are robust, scalable and provide an excellent user experience.

Tecnologias: Elixir, ReactJs, Typescirpt, GraphQL, Amazon S3.

#### Intern CSG International, Londrina

Software Engenieer Intern 05/2023 – 02/2024

I worked on an internship at a multinational company focused on fullstack development, with an emphasis on creating innovative internal solutions. During my experience, I participated in all stages of the software lifecycle, working closely with senior developers and architects, working with the SCRUM framework. Furthermore, as part of my work, I maintain contact with people from different countries, making command of the English language an essential skill, communication is an essential softskill for this work, I have worked throughout the entire life cycle of software, such as CSG People, CSG Track, CSG HUB, CSG COB.

Tecnologies: C#, .NET, ASP.NET, PHP, ReactJS, TypeScript e NextJS

#### Intern, Aitec, Bandeirantes

Scientific Innovation Intern

04/2022 - 05/2023

An internship at AITEC (Agency for Innovation in Technology) an agency of the UENP university (State University of Northern Paraná).

- Responsible for maintenance and new features for the agency's website, which receives hundreds of hits every month.
- 3d modeling of parts and components for projects.
- Laser cuts with a cutter.
- Also the integration and maintenance of technological components for the agency.

Tecnologies: 3D Model, PHP, WordPress, Joolma, Lazer Cut

#### Freelancer

FullStack Developer (<u>Link</u>) 07/2022 - 05/2023

I developed and executed a freelance project, creating an impactful landing page for an online fashion store. The page highlights the store's top products, offering users an immersive visual experience. I implemented a direct redirection system to the owner's WhatsApp when clicking on each piece, facilitating the purchasing process and providing a personalized approach. This contribution resulted in an effective online platform for displaying and selling products, highlighting my ability to create practical and attractive solutions for clients.

Tecnologies: ReactJs, JavaScript, HTML, TailwindCSS e CSS

#### ACADEMIC EDUCATION

#### Computer Science, 2020 - 2024

Computer Science major with specialized skills in programming and software engineering. During my university course, I explored the theory, development and application of computing software and hardware. My passion and aptitude for programming and software engineering led me to focus my studies in this area, where I developed advanced skills in requirements analysis, design, testing and maintenance of software systems. As a result, I am well equipped to create innovative and effective software solutions to solve real, complex problems. I'm excited to continue learning and growing in my career in programming and software engineering.

#### **PROJECTS E INTERESTS**

## First place in Agro Hackaton Genius.con

In 2022, I was recognized as the first place in Agro Hackaton Genius.con. At this event, my team and I developed an innovative agricultural machinery rental platform, focused on meeting the needs of Agro 4.0. This experience allowed me to apply my development and teamwork skills, in addition to improving my skills in technological solutions aimed at the agricultural sector.

## CoinCotatoin App

This app created using ReactNative is used to search for cryptocurrency quotes and information about them, in this app we receive information and data from the Bitcoin and CoinGecko Market APIs. For the future of the project, I think this app will be focused on buying and selling cryptocurrencies, and it will be a social network for people who are interested and working with investments in cryptocurrencies.

# Health App

This application created using ReactNative is used to calculate BMI, conicity index, fat percentage, the app has many other features such as organizing training at the gym and listing and organizing your daily tasks and also as a quick calculator of the same indices.

#### **COURSES**

All of the more than 40 courses I have are available at the link below, covering training in various areas of technology such as Artificial Intelligence, Software Development, Data Science, Agile Methodologies and several others.

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jhonatansilverio/details/certifications/